BLS Collection of Collective Bargaining Agreements (Part 18) 6178/018
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- 8558, 1989-2006 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  7/1989 - 9/1991; 1/1992 - 9/1993; 12/1993 - 9/1997; 9/1995 - 9/2000; 9/1997 - 9/2002; 9/2000 - 9/2006
- 8559, 1999-2005 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  7/1999 - 6/2002 (MOA and agreement); 7/2002 - 6/2005 (XTN)
- 8560, 1997-2007 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2007
- 8561, 1988-2004 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  4/1988 - 6/1993; 6/1996 - 6/2000; 8/1999 - 6/2004
- 8563, 1989-2009 (Box 63, Folder 13)
  5/1989 - 5/1992; 6/1992 - 6/1995; 6/1996 - 6/1998; 6/1998 - 6/2001; 6/2001 - 6/2005; 6/2005 - 6/2009
- 8564, 1997-2008 (Box 63, Folder 14)
  7/1997 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004; 9/2004 - 6/2008
- 8565, 1992-2008 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 5/1999; 5/1999 - 5/2001; 5/1999 - 5/2004; 5/2004 - 5/2008
- 8567, 1989-2004 (Box 63, Folder 16)
  6/1989 - 6/1992; 7/1995 - 7/1996; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004
- 8568, 1995-2004 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  5/1995 - 6/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004
- 8569, 1988-2009 (Box 63, Folder 18)
  5/1988 - 4/1991; 5/1991 - 4/1994; 5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2000 - 4/2004; 5/2000 - 4/2006 (extension); 5/2006 - 4/2009
- 8570, 1990-2004 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2004
- 8571, 1989-2004 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004
- 8572, 1989-2004 (Box 63, Folder 21)
  5/1989 - 4/1991; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004
- 8575, 1996-2007 (Box 63, Folder 22)
  8/1996 - 7/1999; 8/1999 - 7/2002; 8/2002 - 7/2005; 8/2006 - 1/2007
- 8576, 1989-2007 (Box 63, Folder 23)
  7/1989 - 6/1992; 7/1992 - 6/1995; 7/1995 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2007
- 8577, 1993-2005 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  7/1993 - 6/1996; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8578, 1990-2005 (Box 63, Folder 25)
  6/1990; 6/1993; 6/1996; 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8579, 1986-2007 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  8/1986 - 8/1989; 8/1989 - 8/1992; 8/1992 - 8/1995; 8/1995 - 8/1998; 8/1998 - 8/2001; 8/2001 - 8/2004; 8/2004 - 8/2007
- 8581, 1991-2005 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  6/1991 - 4/1995; 4/1995 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2005
- 8582, 1995-2004 (Box 63, Folder 28)
- 8583, 1988-2006 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  6/1988 - 5/1991; 6/1991 - 5/1994; 6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8584, 1997-2007 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  7/1997 - 7/2002; 7/2002 - 7/2007
- 8592, 1989-2003 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  10/1989 - 9/1991; 10/1991 - 9/1994; 10/1994 - 9/1997; 10/1997 - 9/2000; 10/2000 - 9/2003
- 8593, 1990-2005 (Box 64, Folder 4)
- 8594, 1987-2005 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  7/1987 - 6/1991; 7/1994 - 6/1996; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8595, 1995-2005 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  4/1995 - 3/1996; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2005
- 8597, 1989-2001 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  6/1989 - 5/1991 (Extension); 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001
- 8598, 1991-2006 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  4/1991 - 5/1999 (Evergreen); 6/1999 - 5/2003 (wages); 10/2001 - 6/2006
- 8599, 1991-2006 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  6/1991 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2006
- 8600, 1988-2003 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  6/1988 - 5/1990; 6/1990 - 6/1994; 6/1994 - 6/1996; 6/1996 - 6/1999; 6/1999 - 6/2003
- 8601, 1995-2007 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  6/1995 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2007
- 8603, 1998-2006 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- 8604, 1989-2004 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  5/1989 - 5/1992; 5/1992 - 5/1995; 5/1995 - 5/1998; 5/1998 - 5/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004
- 8605, 1989-2004 (Box 64, Folder 14)
  5/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004
- 8606, 1997-2007 (Box 64, Folder 15)
  6/1997 - 5/2003 (Local 612); 6/1997 - 5/2003 (Local 302); 6/2003 - 5/2007 (Both)
- 8608, 1996-2005 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  5/1996 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2000 (wage sheet only); 5/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2005
- 8609, 1990-2005 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  6/1990 - 5/1992; 6/1994 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8610, 1995-2001 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  9/1995 - 8/1998; 9/1998 - 8/2001 (Extension)
- 8612, 1989-2007 (Box 64, Folder 19)
  7/1989 - 6/1992; 7/1992 - 6/1995; 7/1995 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004; 7/2004 - 6/2007
- 8613, 1990-2008 (Box 64, Folder 20)
  4/1990 - 3/1993; 4/1993 - 3/1996; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005; 4/2005 - 3/2008
- 8615, 1994-2005 (Box 64, Folder 21)
  4/1994 - 3/1996; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005
- 8617, 1989-2006 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 7/1995 - 7/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2006
- 8618, 1994-2006 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  7/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2006
- 8619, 1992-2005 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  4/1992 - 3/1993; 4/1995 - 3/1996; 4/1996 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2005
- 8620, 1990-2005 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8622, 1987-2009 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  4/1987 - 3/1990; 8/1990 - 3/1993; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005; 4/2005 - 3/2009
- 8623, 1989-2007 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  7/1989 - 6/1993; 6/1993 - 6/1997; 7/1997 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2003; 7/2003 - 6/2007
- 8624, 1990-2007 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  6/1990 - 3/1993; 4/1993 - 3/1996; 3/1996 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2007
- 8626, 1990-2008 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 5/2002 - 5/2008
- 8627, 1996-2002 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- 8630, 1992-2006 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2006
- 8631, 1992-2004 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  5/1992 - 5/1996; 3/1999 - 3/2004
- 8632, 1987-2008 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  4/1987 - 3/1990; 4/1990 - 3/1993; 4/1993 - 3/1996; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005; 4/2005 - 3/2008
- 8634, 1988-2005 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  5/1988 - 4/1991; 5/1991 - 4/1994; 5/1994 - 6/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2005
- 8635, 1990-2007 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  6/1990 - 4/1991; 11/1991 - 4/1994; 6/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2007
- 8636, 1995-2009 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  6/1995 - 5/1995; 5/1998 - 5/2004; 5/2004 - 5/2009
- 8637, 1987-2004 (Box 65, Folder 16)
  5/1987 - 4/1990; 5/1990 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004
- 8639, 1992-2005 (Box 65, Folder 17)
  7/1992 - 6/1996; 7/1996 - 2/2001; 3/2001 - 2/2005
- 8641, 1996-2005 (Box 65, Folder 18)
  6/1996 - 2/2000; 3/2000 - 2/2005
- 8646, 1988-2006 (Box 65, Folder 19)
  5/1988 - 4/1990; 5/1990 - 4/1992; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2006
- 8647, 1997-2008 (Box 65, Folder 20)
  5/1997 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 5/2005; 5/2008
- 8649, 1989-2007 (Box 65, Folder 21)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 6/1992 - 5/1995; 6/1997 - 5/2002; 6/1997 - 5/2003 (extension); 6/2003 - 5/2007
- 8650, 1989-2007 (Box 65, Folder 22)
  7/1989 - 6/1992; 7/1994 - 6/1997; 7/1997 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2003; 7/2003 - 6/2007
- 8651, 1998-2006 (Box 65, Folder 23)
  8/1998 - 7/2002; 8/2002 - 7/2006
- 8652, 1992-2004 (Box 65, Folder 24)
  5/1992 - 4/1993; 7/1993 - 4/1996; 5/1996 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2002 (Extension); 5/2001 - 4/2004
- 8653, 2001-2004 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- 8655, 2002-2007 (Box 65, Folder 26)
  5/2002 - 4/2007
- 8661, 1989-2004 (Box 65, Folder 27)
  11/1989 - 10/1992; 11/1998 - 10/2001; 11/2001 - 10/2004
- 8663, 1999-2005 (Box 65, Folder 28)
  7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8664, 1990-2008 (Box 65, Folder 29)
  6/1990 - 6/1993; 7/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005; 4/2005 - 3/2008
- 8666, 1989-2003 (Box 65, Folder 30)
  6/1989 - 6/1991; 6/1994 - 6/1997; 6/1997 - 6/2000; 6/2000 - 6/2003
- 8666, 1989-2003 (Box 65, Folder 31)
- 8668, 1989-2008 (Box 65, Folder 32)
  6/1989 - 6/1992; 6/1992 - 6/1995; 6/1995 - 6/1998; 6/1998 - 6/2003; 6/2003 - 6/2008
- 8669, 1993-2006 (Box 65, Folder 33)
  4/1993 - 3/1997; 4/2002 - 3/2006
- 8671, 1997-2007 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  4/1997 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2007
- 8673, 1991-2005 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  7/1991 - 6/1993; 7/1993 - 6/1996; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 3/1998 - 3/2000; 3/2000 - 3/2005
- 8675, 1990-2005 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  7/1990 - 6/1993; 7/1993 - 6/1996; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8676, 1990-2003 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  8/1990 - 7/1993; 8/1993 - 7/1998; 8/1998 - 7/2003
- 8677, 1991-2006 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  7/1991 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2006
- 8678, 1989-2007 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  8/1989 - 7/1992; 8/1992 - 7/1995; 8/1995 - 7/1998; 8/1998 - 7/2002; 8/2002 - 7/2007
- 8679, 1995-2003 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  1/1995 - 12/1997; 1/1998 -12/2000; 4/2001 - 12/2003
- 8680, 1996-2004 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2004
- 8682, 1990-2005 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  3/1990 - 2/1993; 3/1993 - 3/1996; 3/1996 - 3/1999; 3/1999 - 3/2002; 3/2002 - 3/2005
- 8684, 1989-2006 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  7/1989 - 6/1992; 7/1992 - 6/1995; 7/1995 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 9/2001; 10/2001 - 9/2006
- 8687, 1993-2007 (Box 66, Folder 11)
  5/1993 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2007
- 8690, 1988-2004 (Box 66, Folder 12)
  4/1988; 4/1991; 4/1994; 5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2004
- 8691, 1993-2004 (Box 66, Folder 13)
  9/1993 - 7/1995; 8/1995 - 7/1998; 8/1998 - 7/2001; 8/2001 - 7/2004
- 8692, 1993-2003 (Box 66, Folder 14)
  12/1993 - 12/1996; 12/1996 - 12/1999; 12/1999 - 12/2003
- 8696, 1986-2005 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  5/1986 - 4/1989; 5/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2005
- 8697, 1991-2003 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  5/1991 - 4/1994; 5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2003
- 8699, 2001-2006 (Box 66, Folder 17)
  4/2001 - 3/2006
- 8700, 1987-2009 (Box 66, Folder 18)
  7/1987 - 6/1990; 7/1990 - 6/1993; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002 (MOA); 7/2002 - 6/2006 (MOA); 6/2006 - 6/2009 (MOA)
- 8701, 1989-2004 (Box 66, Folder 19)
  7/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 4/2001 - 4/2004
- 8702, 1997-2004 (Box 66, Folder 20)
  9/1997 - 3/2001; 4/2001 - 3/2004
- 8703, 1999-2005 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- 8705, 1990-2005 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- 8707, 1993-2006 (Box 66, Folder 23)
  9/1993 - 8/1995; 9/1995 - 8/1998; 9/1998 - 8/1999; 9/1999 - 8/2002; 9/2002 - 8/2006 (MOA)
- 8708, 1987-2004 (Box 66, Folder 24)
  9/1987 - 8/1992; 9/1992 - 8/1995; 9/1995 - 8/1998; 9/1998 - 8/2001 (summary and wages); 9/2001 - 7/2004
- 8710, 1997-2002 (Box 66, Folder 25)
  4/1997 - 3/2001; 4/1997 - 3/2002
- 8711, 1985-2004 (Box 66, Folder 26)
  4/1985 - 3/1988; 4/1988 - 3/1991; 4/1991 - 3/1994; 4/1994 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2004
- 8712, 1995-2006 (Box 66, Folder 27)
  6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004; 12/2005 - 5/2006
- 8714, 1987-2005 (Box 66, Folder 28)
  7/1987 - 6/1990; 7/1990 - 6/1993; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8715, 1994-2007 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  9/1994 - 9/1997; 9/1997 - 9/2000; 9/2000 - 9/2003; 9/2003 - 9/2007
- 8717, 1988-2004 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  5/1988 - 4/1991; 5/1991 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004
- 8719, 1995-2004 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004
- 8721, 1988-2005 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  5/1988 - 4/1993; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2005
- 8722, 1988-2004 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  5/1988 - 4/1991; 5/1991 - 4/1994; 5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2004
- 8723, 1991-2008 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  4/1991 - 3/1994; 8/1994 - 7/1998; 8/1998 - 7/2003; 9/2003 - 4/2008
- 8724, 2000-2006 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  6/2000 - 6/2003; 6/2003 - 6/2006
- 8725, 1998-2008 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  5/1998 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2008
- 8727, 1987-2006 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  7/1987 - 6/1990; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2006
- 8728, 1999-2006 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2006
- 8731, 1990-2004 (Box 67, Folder 11)
  7/1990 - 6/1993; 7/1993 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2004
- 8734, 1999-2005 (Box 67, Folder 12)
- 8735, 1996-2005 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  3/1996 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2005
- 8736, 1999-2003 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  5/1999 - 4/2003
- 8737, 1992-2005 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  5/1992 - 4/1993; 5/1999 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2005
- 8738, 1989-2005 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  5/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2005
- 8739, 1989-2005 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  5/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1995 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2005
- 8741, 2001-2007 (Box 67, Folder 18)
- 8744, 1988-2006 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  6/1988 - 5/1991; 6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000 (wages); 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8745, 2002-2007 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  6/2002 - 5/2007
- 8747, 1988-2004 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  6/1988 - 5/1991; 6/1997 - 5/2004
- 8748, 1999-2005 (Box 67, Folder 22)
- 8750, 2002-2008 (Box 67, Folder 23)
- 8751, 2002-2008 (Box 67, Folder 24)
- 8754, 1996-2008 (Box 67, Folder 25)
- 8755, 1999-2009 (Box 67, Folder 26)
  7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2006 (MOA); 7/2006 - 6/2009 (MOA)
- 8757, 1996-2007 (Box 67, Folder 27)
  10/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2000 - 4/2004; 7/2004 - 4/2007
- 8762, 1988-2005 (Box 67, Folder 28)
  5/1988 - 4/1991; 4/1997 - 4/2000; 5/2000 - 4/2005
- 8763, 1994-2005 (Box 67, Folder 29)
  9/1994 - 8/1996; 9/1996 - 8/1999; 9/1999 - 8/2002; 9/2002 - 8/2005
- 8764, 1988-2006 (Box 67, Folder 30)
  6/1988 - 5/1991; 6/1992 - 5/1993; 6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8766, 2002-2005 (Box 67, Folder 31)
- 8767, 1989-2008 (Box 67, Folder 32)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 7/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8768, 1997-2008 (Box 67, Folder 33)
  6/1997 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8771, 1999-2007 (Box 67, Folder 34)
  5/1999 - 4/2002; 6/2002 - 4/2007
- 8775, 1988-2006 (Box 67, Folder 35)
- 8776, 1989-2002 (Box 67, Folder 36)
  5/1989 - 7/1992; 5/1996 - 5/1999; 5/1999 - 5/2002
- 8777, 1992-2008 (Box 67, Folder 37)
  6/1992 - 6/1995; 6/1995 - 6/1998; 6/1998 - 6/2003; 6/2003 - 6/2008
- 8778, 1997-2004 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003 (extension); 6/2003 - 5/2004 (extension); 6/2000 - 5/2004 (booklet)
- 8781, 1985-2003 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  9/1985 - 8/1987; 9/1993 - 8/1996; 9/1996 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/2000; 9/2000 - 8/2003
- 8782, 1997-2007 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2007
- 8783, 1993-2006 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  9/1993 - 8/1995; 9/1995 - 8/1998; 9/1998 - 8/1999 (MOA); 9/1999 - 8/2002; 9/2002 - 8/2006
- 8784, 1990-2004 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  8/1990 - 7/1993; 8/1993 - 7/1996; 8/1996 - 7/1999; 8/1999 - 7/2004
- 8788, 1989-2007 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  5/1989 - 5/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2007
- 8789, 1995-2004 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- 8794, 1987-2007 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  8/1987 - 8/1992; 8/1992 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/2002; 9/2002 - 8/2007
- 8796, 1990-2006 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  7/1990 - 6/1993; 7/1993 - 6/1994; 7/1994 - 6/1997; 7/1997 - 6/2000; 6/2000 - 6/2003; 7/2003 - 6/2006
- 8798, 1988-2004 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  4/1988 - 4/1991; 4/1991 - 7/1994; 8/1999 - 7/2004
- 8800, 1990-2007 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  10/1990 - 10/1995; 10/1995 - 10/2000; 10/2000 - 10/2003 (MON); 10/2003 - 6/2007
- 8802, 1995-2007 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  10/1995 - 10/2000; 10/2000 - 10/2003; 12/2003 - 6/2007
- 8803, 1990-2005 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8806, 1990-2005 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/202; 6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8810, 1991-2009 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  5/1991 - 4/1994; 5/1994 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2006; 5/2006 - 4/2009
- 8811, 1988-2004 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- 8813, 1988-2004 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- 8815, 1989-2004 (Box 68, Folder 18)
  5/1989 - 5/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1996; 5/1995 - 4/2001; 5/1995 - 5/2004
- 8816, 2000-2006 (Box 68, Folder 19)
  5/2000 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2006
- 8820, 1988-2005 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  6/1988 - 5/1990; 6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1993 - 5/1996; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005
- 8829, 1990-2005 (Box 68, Folder 21)
  7/1990 - 6/1993; 7/1993 - 6/1996; 7/1996 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8830, 1989-2007 (Box 68, Folder 22)
  5/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 5/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2007
- 8831, 1991-2004 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  9/1991 - 9/1993; 9/1996 - 9/1999; 9/1999 - 9/2004
- 8832, 2000-2006 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  5/2000 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2006
- 8833, 1998-2005 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  7/1998 - 6/2005
- 8834, 1993-2005 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  5/1993 - 6/1997; 5/1997 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8840, 1993-2004 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  1/1993 - 12/1995; 1/1996 - 12/1999; 2/2000 - 12/2004
- 8854, 1989-2010 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 1/1996 - 5/2000; 1/2000 - 6/2010
- 8859, 1992-2007 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  3/1992 - 2/1995; 3/1995 - 2/1998; 3/1998 - 2/2001; 3/2001 - 2/2004; 3/2004 - 2/2007
- 8917, 1996-1999 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  5/1/1996 - 4/30/1999
- 8868, 1996-2006 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  7/1996 - 6/2001; 6/2001 - 6/2006
- 8869, 1990-2004 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2004
- 8870, 2002-2007 (Box 69, Folder 11)
- 8872, 1987-2006 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  7/1987 - 6/1990; 7/1996 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2006
- 8887, 1990-2006 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  9/1990 - 8/1991; 11/1996 - 11/1999; 7/1998 - 5/2000 (Arbitrator's Opinion on Wages); 6/2000 - 5/2003; 2003 - 2006 (IRC Decision); 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8888, 1993-2004 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- 8900, 2003-2006 (Box 69, Folder 15)
- 8902, 2004-2006 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  12/2004 - 12/2006
- 8904, 1995-2007 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  10/1995 - 7/1999; 9/1999 - 7/2003; 8/2003 - 7/2007
- 8908, 1989-2007 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  7/1989 - 6/1992; 7/1992 - 6/1995; 7/1995 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2001; 7/2001 - 6/2004; 7/2004 - 7/2007
- 8910, 1989-2004 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  5/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 6/2001 - 4/2004
- 8912, 2004-2006 (Box 69, Folder 20)
- 8913, 2004-2006 (Box 69, Folder 21)
- 8917, 1996-2004 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  5/1996 - 4/1999; 5/1999 - 4/2004
- 8920, 1988-2004 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  4/1988 - 6/1993; 6/1992 - 6/1997; 6/1997 - 6/2000; 8/1999 - 6/2004
- 8924, 1998-2005 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  7/1998 - 6/2002; 7/2002 - 6/2005
- 8934, 1987-2008 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  10/1987 - 12/1990; 10/1990 - 12/1993; 12/1996 - 12/1999; 12/1999 - 12/2003; 12/2004 - 12/2008
- 8939, 1995-2007 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2004; 6/2004 - 5/2007
- 8941, 1989-2007 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  2/1989 - 1/1992; 2/1992 - 1/1995; 2/1995 - 1/1998; 2/1998 - 1/2001; 2/2001 - 1/2004; 2/2004 - 1/2007
- 8944, 2001-2008 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  8/2001 - 6/2004; 8/2004 - 6/2008
- 8946, 1989-2004 (Box 69, Folder 29)
- 8948, 1981-2007 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  7/1981 - 5/1984; 6/1984 - 5/1987; 6/1987 - 5/1990; 6/1990 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2007
- 8951, 1987-2007 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  8/1987 - 8/1992; 8/1992 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/1998 (extension); 9/1998 - 8/2002 (MOA); 9/1998 - 8/2002 (MOA); 9/1998 - 8/2002 (booklet); 9/2002 - 8/2007
- 8952, 1987-2008 (Box 70, Folder 1)
  8/1987 - 8/1992; 8/1992 - 8/1997; 9/1997 - 8/1998 (extension); 9/1997 - 8/2003; 9/2003 - 8/2008
- 8953, 1987-2009 (Box 70, Folder 2)
  4/1987 - 3/1990; 4/1990 - 3/1993; 4/1993 - 4/1996; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2009
- 8955, 1989-2008 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  5/1989 - 4/1992; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2003; 5/2003 - 4/2008
- 8956, 1990-2003 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  1/1990 - 12/1993; 1/1990 - 12/1994; 1/1995 - 12/1998; 1/1999 - 12/2003
- 8958, 1989-2007 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  12/1989 - 3/1993; 4/1993 - 3/1996; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002 (booklet and MOA); 4/2002 - 3/2005 (MOA and booklet); 4/2006 - 3/2007
- 8959, 1990-2008 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  12/1990; 12/1993; 12/1999; 12/2004 - 12/2008
- 8960, 1988-2008 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  7/1988 - 6/1993; 7/1993 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 6/2003; 7/2003 - 6/2008
- 8961, 1986-2005 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  4/1986 - 5/1990; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 9/2002; 10/2002 - 6/2005
- 8962, 1988-2005 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  8/1988 - 7/1991; 8/1992 - 7/1994; 8/1994 - 7/1997; 8/1997 - 7/2001; 8/2001 - 7/2005
- 8963, 1991-2006 (Box 70, Folder 10)
  4/1991 - 3/1994; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2006
- 8964, 1990-2008 (Box 70, Folder 11)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1996 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2002; 6/2002 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8965, 1994-2005 (Box 70, Folder 12)
  7/1994 - 6/1998; 7/1998 - 9/2001; 10/2001 - 9/2005 (extension)
- 8966, 1988-2006 (Box 70, Folder 13)
  6/1988 - 6/1990; 6/1991 - 3/1994; 7/1997 - 6/2000; 8/2000 - 6/2003; 9/2003 - 12/2006
- 8967, 1988-2006 (Box 70, Folder 14)
  6/1988 - 5/1991; 6/1991 - 5/1993; 6/1996 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8968, 1989-2009 (Box 70, Folder 15)
  5/1989 - 5/1992; 5/1995 - 5/1999; 5/1999 - 5/2004; 5/2004 - 5/2009
- 8969, 1991-2007 (Box 70, Folder 16)
  12/1991 - 4/1995; 4/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2004; 5/2004 - 4/2007
- 8970, 1991-2004 (Box 70, Folder 17)
  6/1991 - 5/1994; 6/1997 -5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 8/2003 - 5/2004
- 8971, 1992-2008 (Box 70, Folder 18)
  5/1992 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2005; 5/2005 - 4/2008
- 8972, 1989-2004 (Box 70, Folder 19)
  6/1989 - 6/1993; 2/1997 - 6/2000; 7/2000 - 6/2004
- 8973, 2000-2006 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8974, 1990-2006 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  6/1990 - 5/1993; 6/1996 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8975, 1988-2008 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  1/1988 - 1/1993; 1/1993 - 1/1998; 1/1998 - 1/2003; 1/2003 - 1/2008
- 8977, 1991-2004 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  8/1991 - 7/1993; 8/1993 - 7/1995 (wages only); 8/1995 - 7/1998; 8/1998 - 7/2001; 8/2001 - 7/2004
- 8978, 1991-2006 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  6/1991 - 5/1994; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 6/2006
- 8980, 1991-2008 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  4/1991 - 3/1994; 4/1994 - 3/1998; 3/1998 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 5/2008
- 8981, 1989-2003 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  6/1989 - 5/1992; 1/1996 - 12/2000; 1/2001 - 12/2003
- 8982, 1997-2008 (Box 71, Folder 8)
  4/1997 - 3/2003; 4/2003 - 3/2008
- 8984, 1991-2008 (Box 71, Folder 9)
  4/1991 - 3/1994; 8/1993 - 7/1998; 8/1998 - 7/2003; 5/2003 - 5/2008
- 8985, 1989-2008 (Box 71, Folder 10)
  6/1989 - 5/1991; 6/1995 - 5/1998; 6/1998 - 5/2001 (wages only); 6/2001 - 5/2005; 6/2005 - 5/2008
- 8986, 1992-2006 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1996 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2006
- 8990, 1991-2006 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  6/1991 - 5/1994; 6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2003; 6/2003 - 5/2006
- 8991, 1989-2003 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  6/1989 - 5/1991; 6/1991 - 5/1993; 6/1997 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2001; 6/2001 - 5/2003
- 8992, 1992-2006 (Box 71, Folder 14)
  5/1992 - 4/1995; 5/1995 - 4/1998; 5/1998 - 4/2002; 5/2002 - 4/2006
- 8993, 1988-2008 (Box 71, Folder 15)
  4/1988 - 3/1991; 4/1991 - 3/1994; 4/1994 - 3/1997; 4/1997 - 3/2000; 4/2000 - 3/2004; 4/2004 - 3/2008
- 8995, 1990-2005 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- 8996, 1991-2005 (Box 71, Folder 17)
  9/1991 - 8/1994; 9/1997 - 8/2000; 9/2000 - 8/2005
- 8997, 1991-2003 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  6/1991 - 5/1995; 6/1995 - 5/1999; 6/1999 - 5/2003
- 8998, 1997-2009 (Box 71, Folder 19)
  6/1997; 7/1997 - 6/2002; 6/2002 - 6/2004; 7/2004 - 6/2009
- 8999, 1988-2004 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  7/1988 - 6/1993; 7/1993 - 6/1996; 7/1996 - 6/1999; 7/1999 - 6/2004
- 9001, 1988-2005 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  5/1988 - 4/1993; 5/1993 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2005
- 9004, 1990-2005 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  4/1990 - 3/1993; 4/1996 - 3/1999; 4/1999 - 3/2002; 4/2002 - 3/2005
- 9005, 1992-2008 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  4/1992 - 4/1997; 5/1997 - 4/2001; 5/2001 - 4/2005; 5/2005 - 4/2008
- 9009, 1994-2005 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  6/1994 - 5/1997; 6/1997 - 5/2000; 6/2000 - 5/2005
- 9012, 1992-2004 (Box 71, Folder 25)